{
    "subject": "resource/Patti_D'Arbanville",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1951-05-25",
    "human_readable": "Patti D'Arbanville was born on May 25th, 1951.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9273265600204468,
            "question": "When was Patti D'Arbanville born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8511817455291748,
            "question": "What century was Patti D'Arbanville born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8464380502700806,
            "question": "What is Patti D'Arbanville's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930827736854553,
            "question": "On what day of the week was Patti D'Arbanville born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731931805610657,
            "question": "Is Patti D'Arbanville a May baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7646588683128357,
            "question": "What month and day was Patti D'Arbanville born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7122763991355896,
            "question": "Patti D'Arbanville was born in the year 19...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6896794438362122,
            "question": "How old is Patti D'Arbanville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5437126159667969,
            "question": "Is Patti D'Arbanville a Taurus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4810347855091095,
            "question": "In what year did Patti D'Arbanville come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Patti D'Arbanville was born on May 25th, 1951.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5075_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Patti D'Arbanville a Taurus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5075_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Patti D'Arbanville?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5075_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Patti D'Arbanville was born in the year 19...?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5075_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5075_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Patti D'Arbanville was born on Friday, May 25th, 1951 and is currently 73 years old.\" This information supports the statement that Patti D'Arbanville was born on May 25th, 1951."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}